Guide to the Goddard Lieberson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1939-1977
  - Lettered correspondence
    - Butterfield, President (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Butz, Carol (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Byer, Louis (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Byers, Montgomery L. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bynner, Witter (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Cabaret Company (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cabezas, Henry (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cade, Tom (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cahan, William & Grace (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Calamita (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - CALCAV (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Callahan, Margaret (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Calmel, Josette (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Calray Gas Service, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Calvi, Maria (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Campbell, Robert G. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Canada Life Insurance (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Canadian Broadcasting (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Canedy, Donald G. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cantor, Gloria (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Capehart, James (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Caplan, Frank (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Capote, Truman (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cappelen, Hans (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Capra, Remo (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Captain Haggerty's School for Dogs (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carisi, Irma (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carle, Rene (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carlson, Leonard (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Hall (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carpenter, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carpentier, Alejo (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carriage House (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carroll, Alice (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carson-Selman, Richard (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Elliot (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Ralph, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cartier, Jacques (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cartwright's (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Casadesus, Evie (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Casadesus, Gaby (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Casadesus, Guy (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Casadesus, Robert (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Casals, Pablo & wife (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cash, Johnny (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cash Productions (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cassel, Alvin (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cassidy, Claudia (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cassidy, Jack & Shirley (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Caston, Saul (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cates, Gilbert (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Cato, Robert (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Catton, Bruce (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Cavett, Dick (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - CBS (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Celler, Emanuel (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Centerline (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Century Advent Recording Corp. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Century Association (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cerf, Bennett (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cerutti, Silvio (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chamberlin, Ann (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chapin, Schuyler G. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chaplin, Charles & Donna (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chappell Music Co. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Charles-David, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Charles H. Stern Agency (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chase, Gilbert (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chase, Ilka (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chavez, Carlos (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chemical Bank (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chenkin, Victor (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cheryl Crawford Productions (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chevalier, Maurice (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cheyette, Herbert (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chicago (Band) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Musical College (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Public Television (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Children's Asthma Research Institute & Hospital (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Children's Book Shop (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chin, Ng Lian (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Choate School (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Choice Magazine Listening (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chotzinoff, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chung, Won K. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Church of the Heavenly Rest (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Church of the Holy Communion (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cinchpac of Vermont (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cinema Center (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Circle in the Square (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of NY (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - City College NY (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - City of New York (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Civic Light Opera (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Civil War Round Table (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Claddagh Records (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Claridge's (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Freeman (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Kenneth B. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Sam H. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clement, Frank G. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clements, Robert (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland Institute of Music (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland Orchestra (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clooney, Rosemary (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clurman, Richard M. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clurman, Shirley (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Adelle (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Alexander (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Harriet (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Kip (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Sabrina (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohn, Frederick (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cohn, Marvin (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Colasanti, Veniero & John Moore (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Coleman, Cy (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Cole Porter Musical & Literary Property Trusts (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Colin, Ralph F. & Georgia (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - College of Santa Fe (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Colleretto (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Collier, John (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Collins, Earl (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Colonial Gift Shop (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Columbia University (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Columbia Artists Management (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Comden, Betty & Adolph Green (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cominsky, Jack R. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Commander Publications (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Commentary (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Puerto Rico (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Composers Ensemble (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Composers Lyricists Educational Foundation (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Concert Artists Guild, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conde Nast Publications (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conference of Personal Managers East, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Continental Marketing Corporation (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conklin, William T. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conkling, James B. & Donna (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conly, John M. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Connelly, Marc (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Conniff, Mr. & Mrs. Ray (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Constance Hope Associates (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cook, Dr. CA (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cook, Eugene (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cook's Geranium Nursery (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Coolidge, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cooper, A.S. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Copland, Aaron (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Coppola, Piero (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corigliano, John (Sr.) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corigliano, John (Jr.) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corte-Real, Roberto (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corvin, Maria (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corwin, Norman (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Costello, Del (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Costin, Glen G. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cot, Alexandra (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cott, Jonathan (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cotton, Dorothy W. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Country Music Association (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Courtney, Stephanie (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cousins, Norman (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cowan, Louis (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Coward, Noel (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cowell, Henry (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Cowles, Gardner & Jan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cowley, Susan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cox, Ainslee (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cracovaner, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Craft, Rob (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Craig Corporation (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Craig, Wendy (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Crawdaddy Publishing (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Crawford, Cheryl (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Crawford, Joan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Crawford, Morris (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Creative Artists Public Service Program (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Creative Music Foundation, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Creative Playthings (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Crenesse, Pierre (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Creston, Paul (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cronkite, Walter (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Cronyn, Hume (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crosby, Bing (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crosby, John (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crosby, Suzanne (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crouse, Anna (Mrs. Russel) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crouse, Russel (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crouse, Tim (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crowe, Gordon (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crowley, Suzanne (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Crutchfield, Charles (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cucchia, Mrs. Joseph (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Culshaw, John (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cultural Foundation of Boston (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cummings, Nathan (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cummings, e.e. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Current Biography (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Curtis Institute (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cywarch, Glyn (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - D'Arcy, Martin (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - D'Arms, Edward (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dahl, Katherine (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dahl, Roald (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dahl Smith Tailors (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dakota, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Dalton School (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Daniel, Clifton and Margaret (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Daniels, Edward B. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Daniels, Ralph (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Darrell, Rob D. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Darrow, Jason (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dartmouth Arts Council (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - David Hochstein Memorial Music School (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davidson, Ronald T.H. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davidson, Robert (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davies, Gillian (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Allen (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Clive (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Davis Polk & Wardell (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Sammy, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Stuart (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dawidowicz, Michal (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dawson, Tom (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Day, Doris (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Day Treatment Center, VA (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - D'Erlanger, Rodolphe (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De La Grange, Baron Henri-Louis (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Liagre, Mrs. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Rougemont, Denis (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Rougemont, Peter (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Sylva, B.G. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Tinan, Madame D.G. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - De Valera, Eamon (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - de Voss, Ltd. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Del Rio, Jesus (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Dell' Olio, Anselma (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - DeVoto, Bernard (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Dean, Walter L. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Degamo Productions (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Delaware River Terminal, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Delorme, M. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Delza, Sophia (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Denney, Nicolas (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Denhard & Stewart (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Denker Music Limited (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Desmond, Jody (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - D.H. Wolfe & Associates (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Diamond, David (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Diamond, Neil (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Diapason (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dickson, Harry Ellis (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - The Diebold Group, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dietrich, Marlene (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dietz, Howard & Lucinda (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Diller-Quaile School of Music, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Diller, Phyllis (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - The Disc Shop (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Discophile, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Discos CBS (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dispeker, Thea (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Distinctive Diaries, Ltd. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dmytryszyn, Steve (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Doehrman, EW (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dolan, Patrick (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Donegan, Bishop Horace W.B. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Donehue, Vincent (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dorati, Antal (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dorff, Norman (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dorfsman, Lou (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dorn, Ken (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dorso, Richard (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dos Passos, John (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Doubleday & Co. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Douglas, Kirk (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Douglas L. Elliman & Co. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dover Publications (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dowdey, Clifford (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Downes, Olin (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Drake, Alfred (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Drew, David (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dreyfus, Mrs. Louis (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dreyfus, Max (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Driscoll-Wells Production Co. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Drogheda, Lady Joan (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dry Dock Savings Bank (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Du Bose, Beverly (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Duchin, Eddy (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Duchin, Peter (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dufallo, Richard (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Duffu, John J. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dufty, William (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dulac's Language Conversation School (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dumore, Dick (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dunhill's (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dunn, Winfield (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Durgom, George Bullets (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Duryea, Perry B. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dylan, Bob & Sarah (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Earl, Al (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - East 60's Property Owners Association (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - East Village Other (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eastern New Mexico University (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eastman School of Music (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eckels, George (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eddy, Nelson (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Edelman, Gerald (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Edelweiss Gardens (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Editions Recontre and Erik Nitsche International (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Editions Salabert (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Edman, Irwin (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Edouard & Butler, Ltd. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Edward, Alfred C. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Einstein, Albert (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Eisler, Hans (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ekstrom, Mr. and Mrs. Arne (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Elektra Records (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Eliasberg, Jan (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Queen Elisabeth of Belgium (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Elkins Productions International Corporation (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ellington, Duke (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ellis Music Enterprises, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ellison, Ralph (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - EMI Australia (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Encounter, Ltd. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Engel, Lehman (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Epstein, Alan (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Epstein, Daniel (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Erickson, Mrs. R.J. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Erskine, Pauline (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Esquire Magazine (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Etler, Alvin (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theater (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Evans, Robert V. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Evans/Greengrass, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Everett, Richard D. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Evergreen Review (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Executives Unlimited, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Express Exchange (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fadiman, Clifton (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fagneray, Hubert (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fairbanks, Bing (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas & Mary Lee (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fairfield Library Board (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fairmont Hotel (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Faith, Perry (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - The Family Handiman (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Farat (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Faraway Productions AG (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Farbar, Bernard (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Farnsley, Charlie (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Farr, Wornall F. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fehr, Rudi (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Feiffer, Jules (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fender Musical Instruments (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ferber, Edna (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ferguson, Robert V. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fernandez, John & Lilly (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ferrer, José (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ferrier, Kathleen (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ferry House (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Feuer, Cy (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fields, Dorothy (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Figdale, Robert (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fencher, B. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Finck Floral (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fincke, H.G. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fine, Sylvia (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fink, Morton (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Finkelstein, Harry (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Finletter, Thomas K. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Finney, Albert (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Firkusny, Rudolf (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fitelson, H. William (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fitzgerald, Edward E. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fitzgerald, Frances (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Flaxman, John (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fleischman, Ernest (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Flora, James (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Flora Roberts Inc. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The Florida State University (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Floris (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Foglesong, James S. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foldes, Andor (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Folsom, Frank M. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fontbonne Academy (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fonteyn, Margot (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Forbes, Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Force, Brute (Stephen Friedland) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ford, Charles (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Forest City Public Library (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Forrest, Chet (George) & Robert Wright (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fortas, Abe (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fortnum & Mason LTD (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fortune (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fosburgh, James (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foss, Lukas (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foss, Wenche (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foster & Son (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foster, Laura & Fred (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foster, Micki (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foster Parents Plan (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fox, Annie (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Foy, Gray (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Francescatti, Zino & Yolanda (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Frank Smythson Ltd. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Franklin, Desiree L. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Franks, Tillman (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fratelli Fabbri (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fredericks, Edward B. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Free Library of Philadelphia (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Freed, Richard (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Freedman, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Freedman, Ellis J. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Fremstad, Olive (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fried, Maurice (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friedman, J. Roger (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friendly, Fred (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friends of Hopkins Center (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friends of the Maurice Ravel Academy (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friends of Music Theater, Lincoln Center (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Friends of the Philharmonic (NYC) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fries, Julia (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fritchey, Clayton (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Frolov, O.T. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Frost, Robert (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Frost, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Frothingham, David (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fujita, S. Neil (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fulbright, J.W. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fuller, Stephanie (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fullerton Chamber of Commerce (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Funk & Wagnalls, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Furth, George (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Furtwängler, Mrs. Wilhelm (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Furukaki, Tetsuro (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fusako, Amachi (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - G. Heywood Hill (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gaisberg, Fred (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Galbraith, John (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gallagher, Rosemary (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gallagher, William P. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gallo, Eric & Peggy (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gambit, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garabedian, Lillian (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garbo, Greta (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garden, Mary (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garfunkel, Arthur (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garrison, Lloyd (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Garson, Jean (Mrs. Herbert L.) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gartenberg, Seymour (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gates, William (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gauthier, Eva (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gavin, Bill (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Geffen, David (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gelatt, Roland (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gelb, Bruce S. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gelbetz, Itor (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Geller, Uri (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Geneen, Harold S. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gentele, Janette (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gentele, Marit & Goeran (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Geo. W. Park Seed Company Inc. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - George, Clark B. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - George W. George Productions (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - George W. Henry Foundation (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Georgia State University (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gerard, Rolf (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gerome, Raymond (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gerschefski, Eduin (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gershe, Leonard (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gershwin, Ira (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gesar, Martin Th. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Giannini, Giuseppe (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gielgud, John (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gil Music Corporation (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gilbert, Henry (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gilbert, Richard & Charlotte (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gillian, Terry (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gilroy, Frank (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Girard Nurseries (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Glancy, Kenneth (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gleason, Marion (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gleitsman, Alan (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Glennon, William (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Glenville, Peter (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Glotz, Michel (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gobeille, Richard G. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goelet, Frances (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gold, Jack (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldman, Elliot (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldmark, Peter (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldmark, Rubin (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldsmith's (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldstein, Milton (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goldwyn, Samuel (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Golembo, Arnold (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Golschmann, Vladimir (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Goodman, Benny (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Frederic (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Lord (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Goody, Sam (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gordon, Mary (Mrs. Charles W.) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gordon, Max (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gordon, Ruth (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gorman, Ray (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gortikov, Stan (RIAA) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gothard, Louis (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gottfried, Martin (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Gould, Alfred (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gould, Elliott (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gould, Glenn (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gould, Leslie (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gould, Morton (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gould, Walter (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Graber, Edward A. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Grade, Lew (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Graham, Katherine (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gramm, Donald (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Gramophone (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gran, John (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Granata, Robert J. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Grand Hotel (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Granz, Norman (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Graudan, Joanna (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Graves, Robert (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Green, Adolph (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Green, Johnny (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Green, Nancy (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Greenberg, Noah (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Greenspon, Herbert M. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Greenwald, Harold ("Hal" - Nephew) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gregory, Andre & Chiquita (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gregory, George (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Grey, Madeleine (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Greystone Corporation (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Griffith, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Grimes, Tammy (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Groothuis (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gross, Alfred A. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gross, Jerry (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Grossman, Sam (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gruen, Michael (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gruenberg, Mrs. Louis (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guber (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guercio, James W. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guerlain [?] (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guese (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guest, Mrs. Polk (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Guettel, Henry (Box 8, Folder 9)